{
    "id": "3838d9784762435a976a3b2ae042556a",
    "title": "Grammar exercise: much or many",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "64a3855289cb40db8ee2f702b1210539",
            "title": "Much And Many",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t got …………………. time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ……………….. the roof needs repairing?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "much of",
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can have as ……………….. chocolates as you want.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can stay for as ………………… days as you want.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There aren’t ………………… large eggs left.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You won’t be able to see ……………….. a country in a week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you skip too ……………….. your classes, you won’t pass the exam.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of",
                        "much",
                        "much of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "How …………………. you will be there?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You didn’t eat …………………. breakfast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was so ………………… traffic that it took me two hours to get to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}